http://www.wheelingnailers.com/en/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyEffective date: September 25, 2018Wheeling Nailers ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.wheelingnailers.com/ website (hereinafter referred to as the "Service").This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for Wheeling Nailers is managed with the help of Privacy Policies.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from http://www.wheelingnailers.com/Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataWheeling Nailers uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Wheeling Nailers will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal RequirementsWheeling Nailers may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Wheeling NailersTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enLinks To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children's PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: info@wheelingnailers.com
3C28B153-9335-47C6-8182-EDA512A3BB12
Created with sketchtool.
Star 2 Copy
Created with Sketch.
83849D66-8CC8-47EF-8FF3-576CCFD2EB58
Created with sketchtool.
Artboard
Created with Sketch.
Reading Royals R Logo (1)
Group 106
Created with Sketch.
mavs_circle_logo
Created with Sketch.
K-Wings Color
Created with Sketch.
Fav_icon@1x
Created with Sketch.
Icon / Social / Android@3x
Created with Sketch.
icon-dropdown
Created with Sketch.
Check
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
Created with Sketch.
ADIRONDACK_THUNDER_primary_logo_REV2018@1x
Created with Sketch.
echllogoeps
Created with Sketch.
Group 18 Copy
Created with Sketch.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
team-logo / WIN
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PW
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / LOST
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PL
Created with Sketch.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
7CB4E955-9512-49F4-B03B-933CF03CA2FD
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Search/1000
F3916FC0-768E-4027-A1D5-CC66110459CF
Created with sketchtool.
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Attachment/1000
Created with Sketch.
CB_Linked_Icon_Arrow
